AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records on Microfilm 5478 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Sub-Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.10) (Reel 35)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 35)
      Code no. MC-131-3B-87: Philadelphia and Reading Railroad. November 25, 1921 - December 6, 1921
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.11) (Reel 36)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-335-3B-88: San Antonio, Uvalde and Gulf Railroad. November 19, 1921 - June 20, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-456-3B-89: Northern Pacific Terminal Railroad. November 23, 1921 - December 14, 1921
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-105-3B-90: Macon, Dubin and Savannah Railway. November 22, 1921 - January 6, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-80-3B-91: Kanawha and Michigan Railroad. November 19, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-3-3B-92: Arizona and Eastern Railway. November 19, 1921 - June 17, 1924
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-242-3B-93: San Antonio and Aransaw Pass Railroad. November 19, 1921 - February 24, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-156-3B-94: Seaboard Air Line Railroad. November 24, 1921 - May 10, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-16-3B-95: Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad. November 22, 1921 - March 15, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 9 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-465-3B-96: Union Stock Yard Railroad. November 26, 1921 - December 15, 1921
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 10 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-158-3B-97: Southern Railway. November 28, 1921 - April 10, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 11 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-232-3B-98: Virginian Railway. November 19, 1921 - March 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 12 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-428-3B-99: Camas Prairie Railway. November 28, 1921 - December 21, 1921
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 13 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-310-3B-100: Central Indiana Railroad. November 19, 1921 - January 30, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 14 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-49-3B-101: El Paso and Southwestern Railroad. November 28, 1921 - January 26, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 15 (Reel 36)
      Code no. MC-93-3B-102: Louisville and Nashville Railroad. November 19, 1921 - February 24, 1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.12) (Reel 37)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 37)
      Code no. MC-93-3B-102: Louisville and Nashville Railroad: November 11, 1921 - February 24, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 37)
      Code no. MC-203-3B-104: Gulf and Ship Island Railroad: November 23, 1921 - May 8, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 37)
      Code no. MC-114-3B-105: New Orleans and Great Northern Railroad. November 21, 1921 - June 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 37)
      Code no. MC-144-3B-106: Pullman Company: November 19, 1921 - July 1, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 37)
      Code no. MC-170-3B-107: Trans-Mississippi Terminal Railroad: November24, 1921 - December 20, 1921
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 37)
      Code no. MC-189-3B-108: Western Pacific Railroad: November 19, 1921 -March 2, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 37)
      Code no. MC-455-3B-109: Kansas City, Clinton and Springfield Railroad. December 1, 1921 - January 6, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 37)
      Code no. MC-79-3B-110: Kansas City Terminal Railroad: November 26, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 9 (Reel 37)
      Code no. MC-101-3B-111: Kansas, Oklahoma and Gulf Railway. December 1, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 10 (Reel 37)
      Code no. MC-448-3B-112: Staten Island Rapid Transit Railway. December 1, 1921 - March 16, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 11 (Reel 37)
      Code no. MC-169-3B-113: Texas and Pacific Railroad: November 26, 1921 - February 28, 1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.13) (Reel 38)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 38)
      Code no. MC-106-3B-115: Manistique and Lake Superior Railway. December 3, 1921 - March 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 38)
      Code no. MC-51-3B-116: Florida East Coast Railroad: December 1, 1921 - March 10, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 38)
      Code no. MC-211-3B-117: Spokane, Portland and Seattle Railway: November 19, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 38)
      Code no. MC-184-3B-118: Wabash Railroad: November 20, 1921 - April 8, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 38)
      Code no. MC-137-3B-119: Pittsburg and Shawmut Railroad: November 18, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 38)
      Code no. MC-46-3B-120: Duluth, Missabe and Northern Railroad: December 6, 1921 - February 27, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 38)
      Code no. MC-430-3B-121: Lake Superior and Ishpeming Railroad. December 3, 1921 - March 2, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 38)
      Code no. MC-429-3B-122: Minnesota, Dakota and Western Railway: December 7, 1921 - February 7, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 9 (Reel 38)
      Code no. MC-95-3B-123: Maine Central Railroad: December 8, 1921 - March 29, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 10 (Reel 38)
      Code no. MC-4-3B-124: Georgia Railroad: December 9, 1921: December 17, 1921
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 11 (Reel 38)
      Code no. MC-52-3B-125: Fort Smith and Western Railroad. November 19, 1921 - March 15, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 12 (Reel 38)
      Code no. MC-151-3B-126: Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad: November 21, 1921 - February 23, 1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.14) (Reel 39)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 39)
      Code no. MC-25-3B-127: Chicago and Northwestern Railway: November 21, 1921 - April 25, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 39)
      Code no. MC-78-3B-128: Jacksonville Terminal Railroad: December 13, 1921 - March 20, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 39)
      Code no. MC-469-3B-129: Chicago, Memphis and Gulf Railroad: November 25, 1921: November 30, 1921
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 39)
      Code no. MC-42-3B-130: Denver and Salt Lake Railroad: December 17, 1921 - May 11, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 39)
      Code no. MC-123-3B-131: Northwestern Pacific Railroad: December 19, 1921 - April 3, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 39)
      Code no. MC-60-3B-132: Gulf Coast Lines Railroad: November 25, 1921 - March 3, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 39)
      Code no. MC-412-3B-133: Monongahela Railroad: December 21, 1921 - February 24, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 39)
      Code no. MC-85-3B-134: Louisville, Henderson and St. Louis Railroad. December 22, 1921 - March 20, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 9 (Reel 39)
      Code no. MC-193-3B-135: Atlanta and West Point Railroad: December 19, 1921 - February 25, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 10 (Reel 39)
      Code no. MC-197-3B-137: Railway Association of Canada: December 2, 1921 - September 18, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 11 (Reel 39)
      Code no. MC-96-3B-138: Midland Valley Railroad: December 15, 1921 - February 24, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 12 (Reel 39)
      Code no. MC-138-3B-139: Pittsburg and West Virginia Railroad: November 15, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 13 (Reel 39)
      Code no. MC-90-3B-140: Louisiana and Arkansas Railway: November 30, 1921 - July 20, 1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.15) (Reel 40)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-207-3B-141: Chicago Junction Railway: November 19, 1921 - March 2, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-215-3B-142: Charleston and Western Carolina Railroad. January 1, 1922: February 18, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-62-3B-143: Georgia Railroad: November 23, 1921 - March 1, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-94-3B-144: Michigan Central Railroad: November 18, 1921 - May 15, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-59-3B-145: Gulf, Florida and Alabama Railroad: January 9, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-92-3B-146: Lehigh and New England Railroad: December 13, 1921 - May 17, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-117-3B-147: Baltimore and Ohio Chicago Terminal Railroad. December 30, 1921 - March 1, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-186-3B-148: Washington Terminal Railroad: November 20, 1921: July 5, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 9 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-88-3B-150: Long Island Railroad: January 12, 1922 - March 11, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 10 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-13-3B-151: Bangor and Aroostook Railroad: December 19, 1921 - March 13, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 11 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-73-3B-152: Huntingdon and Broad Top Mountain Railroad and Coal Co.: January 20, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 12 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-363-3B-153: Fort Dodge, Des Moines and Southern Railroad. February 4, 1922 - May 24, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 13 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-103-3B-154: Mobile and Ohio Railroad. May 3, 1921 - February 21, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 14 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-216-3B-155: Alabama and Vicksburg Railway: January 9, 1922 - February 24, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 15 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-473-3B-156: Sioux City Terminal Railroad: February 18, 1922 - March 16, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 16 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-159-3B-157: Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis. December 1, 1921 - March 29, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 17 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-43-3B-158: Delaware and Hudson Railroad: February 18, 1922: February 24, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 18 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-241-3B-159: Indianapolis Union Railroad: February 27, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 19 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-165-3B-160: St. Joseph Belt Railway: February 10, 1922 - March 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 20 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-474: -3B- 161Columbus and Greenville Railway- January 3, 1922 - March 2, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 21 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-172-3B-162: Texas Midland Railroad: November 28, 1921 - March 15, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 22 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-427-3B-163: Carolina, Clinchfield and Ohio Railroad. December 27, 1921 - March 15, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 23 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-102-3B-164: Mississippi Central Railroad: December 14, 1921 - July 3, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 24 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-444-3B-166: Davenport, Rock Island and North Western Railway. March 11, 1922 - March 15, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 25 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-307-3B-167: Memphis Union Depot Railroad. March 10, 1922 - April 1, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 26 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-0-3B-168: Lenoir Car Works. March 13, 1922 - March 18, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 27 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-153-3B-169: St. Louis Southwestern Railway: February 17, 1922: June 9, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 28 (Reel 40)
      Code no. MC-434-3B-170: Louisiana-Southern Railway. October 17, 1921 - June 13, 1922
- Sub-Series 22: 1922 Strike Files, 1922-1925
  Code no. Reels 41-87. This series continues the story of the 1922 Strike and the negotiations leading up to the Strike which are documented in the proceeding two series. Most of the critical documents cover the period 1922-25, but there are also scattered
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.1) (Reel 41)
    - Correspondence from Senators and Representatives to U.S. Department of Labor and Railroad Managements, 1924; 1 (Reel 41)
      Code no. 3C-General: negotiation efforts to settle railroad strikes on Missouri Pacific, Rock Island, Chicago and Eastern Illinois, Wabash and Frisco Railroad. 1922 - January 19, 1924
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.2) (Reel 42)
    - Miscellaneous, 1924; 1 (Reel 42)
      Code no. 3C-General: January 26, 1924
    - Lehigh and New England Railroad, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 42)
      Code no. 3C-2: June 24, 1922 - June 29, 1923
    - Gulf and Ship Island Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 42)
      Code no. 3C-3: June 27, 1922 -March 14, 1923
    - San Diego and Arizona Railway, 1922-1923; 4 (Reel 42)
      Code no. 3C-4: June 25, 1922 - March 16, 1923
    - Pacific Fruit Express, 1922-1923; 5 (Reel 42)
      Code no. 3C-5: June 22, 1922 - August 9, 1923
    - Arizona Eastern Railroad, 1922-1923; 6 (Reel 42)
      Code no. 3C-6: June 27, 1922 - August 9, 1923
    - Philadelphia and Reading Railroad, 1922-1923; 7 (Reel 42)
      Code no. 3C-7: May 30, 1922 - September 19, 1923
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1925-1951; 8 (Reel 42)
      Code no. 3C-8: October 1, 1925 - January 18, 1951
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.3) (Reel 43)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1916-1925; 1 (Reel 43)
      Code no. 3C-8; March 17, 1916 - September 18, 1925
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 2 (Reel 43)
      Code no. 3C-8: Clippings
    - Ann Arbor Railroad, 1922-1939; 3 (Reel 43)
      Code no. 3C-9: June 29, 1922 - December 19, 1939
    - Canadian Railway, 1922-1923; 4 (Reel 43)
      Code no. 3C-10: June 19, 1922 - March 19, 1923
    - Northwest Railroads, 1922-1923; 5 (Reel 43)
      Code no. 3C-11: September 21, 1922 - December 20, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.4) (Reel 44)
    - Northwest Railroads, 1922; 1 (Reel 44)
      Code no. 3C-11: August 31, 1922 - July 19, 1922
    - Carolina, Clinchfield and Ohio Railroad, 1922-1940; 2 (Reel 44)
      Code no. 3C-12: June 28, 1922 - December 12, 1940
    - Peoria and Pekin Union Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 44)
      Code no. 3C-13: June 27, 1922 - November 30, 1923
    - Detroit and Mackinac Railroad, 1922; 4 (Reel 44)
      Code no. 3C-14: June 29, 1922 -April 2, 1924
    - New Orleans and Great Northern Railroad, 1924; 5 (Reel 44)
      Code no. 3C-15: June 27, 1922 - November 21, 1922
    - Communications (includes bulletins), 6 (Reel 44)
      Code no. 3C-16 pt.1: Addressed to the Executive Council and copies of all important letters addressed to President Jewell and Secretary Scott, Bulletins #15-51
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.5) (Reel 45)
    - Communications (includes bulletins), 1922; 1 (Reel 45)
      Code no. 3C-16 pt.1: Addressed to the Executive Council and copies of all important letters addressed to President Jewell and Secretary Scott, Bulletins. June 27, 1922 -October 30, 1922
    - Communications (includes bulletins), 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 45)
      Code no. 3C-16 pt.2: Addressed to the Executive Council and copies of all important letters addressed to President Jewell and Secretary Scott, Bulletins. December 15, 1922 - March 30, 1923
    - Communications (includes bulletins), 1922; 3 (Reel 45)
      Code no. 3C-16 pt.2: Addressed to the Executive Council and copies of all important letters addressed to President Jewell and Secretary Scott, Bulletins. October 31, 1922 - December 15, 1922
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.6) (Reel 46)
    - Communications (includes bulletins), 1923; 1 (Reel 46)
      Code no. 3C-16 pt.31: Addressed to the Executive Council and copies of all important letters addressed to President Jewell and Secretary Scott, Bulletins. April 4, 1923 -December 26, 1923
    - Gulf Mobile and Northern Railway, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 46)
      Code no. 3C-17: June 30, 1922 - October 8, 1923
    - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1922-1935; 3 (Reel 46)
      Code no. 3C-18: August 5, 1922 - May 27, 1935
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.7) (Reel 47)
    - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 47)
      Code no. 3C-18: June 27, 1922 - August 5, 1922
    - Cincinnati, Indianapolis and Western Railway, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 47)
      Code no. 3C-19: June 27, 1922 - March 22, 1923
    - San Antonio and Arkansas Pass Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 47)
      Code no. 3C-20: July 30, 1922 - January 25, 1923
    - De Queen and Eastern - Texas Oklahoma and Eastern Railway, 1922-1925; 4 (Reel 47)
      Code no. 3C-21: June 29, 1922 - March 14, 1925
    - Green Bay and Western Railroad, 1922-1923; 5 (Reel 47)
      Code no. 3C-22: June 30, 1922 - February 19, 1923
    - New York, Ontario and Western Railroad, 1922-1924; 6 (Reel 47)
      Code no. 3C-23: August 28, 1922 - May 19, 1924
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.8) (Reel 48)
    - New York, Ontario and Western Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 48)
      Code no. 3C-23: June 27, 1922 - August 27, 1922
    - St. Louis Terminal Railroad, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 48)
      Code no. 3C-24: June 27, 1922 - May 12, 1923
    - Rutland Railroad, 1922-1925; 3 (Reel 48)
      Code no. 3C-25: June 27, 1922 - February 25, 1925
    - Pittsburg and West Virginia Railroad, 1922-1923; 4 (Reel 48)
      Code no. 3C-26: June 27, 1922 - November 22, 1923
    - Tennessee Central Railroad, 1922; 5 (Reel 48)
      Code no. 3C-27: July 1, 1922 - November 6, 1922
    - Monongahela Railway, 1922-1924; 6 (Reel 48)
      Code no. 3C-28: June 20, 1922 - December 3, 1924
    - Nashville, Chattanooga and St. Louis Railway, 1922-1923; 7 (Reel 48)
      Code no. 3C-29: June 27, 1922 - December 5, 1923
    - Nickel Plate Railroad, 1923; 8 (Reel 48)
      Code no. 3C-30: June 21, 1923 - September 27, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.9) (Reel 49)
    - Nickel Plate Railroad, 1922-1923; 1 (Reel 49)
      Code no. 3C-30: June 27, 1922 - June 20, 1923
    - New York Central Lines, 1922; 2 (Reel 49)
      Code no. 3C-31 pt.1: February 16, 1922 - September 19, 1922